(Penny(waking up):)Okay, look.
(Penny(waking up):)This never happened.
(Penny(waking up):)Do you understand me?
Really?! Still
can't talk to me?
(Leonard:)What are you
doing here?
(Howard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I said, what are you doing here?
(Leonard:)I live here.
(Sheldon:)I have paperwork
that says differently.
(Leonard:)Priya's going back to India.
(Sheldon:)Irrelevant.
(Sheldon:)Rajesh and I have
a good thing going
(Sheldon:)and you're not going to ruin it.
(Leonard:)What are you doing here?
(Howard:)I've been up all night.
(Howard:)- I had a fight with Bernadette.
- Why?
(Howard:)She gave me
a beautiful watch.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, do you
understand this?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Talk to him.
(Penny(entering room dishevelled, with a half naked Raj behind):)Damn.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Leonard:)Oh...
It's-it's not what
it looks like.
(Sheldon:)What does it look like?